Wayne Farrugia

- 3, Bethsalem, Tank Street, SGW3413 Siggiewi (Malta)

Dear Sir/Madam,

I am a Maltese, 20 year old full-time student at University of Malta, studying Banking and Finance and Accounting. I am currently in my second year of studies. I am looking for a part-time job with the availability of working for a maximum of 20 hours per week (since this is stipulated by the requirements of the university).

In terms of work experience, I work as a summer intern for an audit firm (as it compliments my area of study and helps me to gain practical work experience). I have worked there for two consecutive years, and I have the same contract for this year (period between July and September, working 6 hours per day). This would still allow me to work during the summer period, as I would not have any university lectures during that time. This additional working experience helps me to meet and discuss with different employees and clients, which is also an essential part of this job position.

I hope to hear back from your end, as I look forward to start a new experience such as this, whilst continuing my studies.

Thank you for your time and consideration.

Wayne Farrugia



PERSONAL INFORMATION

Wayne Farrugia

3, Bethsalem, Tank Street, SGW3413 Siggiewi (Malta)

79497585

x wayne.farrugia2015@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

University student

WORK EXPERIENCE

14/07/2018-09/07/2019

Transaction Advisory Services Junior Associate

Grant Thornton, Birkirkara (Malta)

- constructing tender proposals
- interpretation of figures and financial statements
- research and data collection
- stock-taking of clients stores
- meetings with clients and training

10/07/2019-16/09/2019

Local Tax Junior Associate

Grant Thornton, Birkirkara (Malta)

- tax returns
- internal workings
- legal implications

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

25/09/2011-28/04/2016

Matsec Certificate

St. Ignatius College, Qormi (Malta)

General

Mathematics (Grade 1)

Maltese (Grade 2)

English Language (Grade 3)

English Literature (Grade 2)

Religion (Grade 1)

Physics (Grade 1)

Options

Environmental (Grade 2)

Business Studies (Grade 1)

Social Studies (Grade 1)

Italian (Grade 1)

GSCE EQF level 3

EQF level 3

euro*pass*

Curriculum vitae

Wayne Farrugia

Accounts (Grade B)

English Language (Grade B)

01/10/2016-31/03/2018

Matriculation Certificate

EQF level 4

G.F. Abela Junior College, Imsida (Malta)

Advanced Level

Accounts (Grade A)

Marketing (Grade B)

Intermediary Level

Pure Mathematics (Grade A)

Information technology (Grade A)

English (Grade C)

Systems of Knowledge (Grade B)

01/10/2018-Present

Bachelor of Commerce in Accountancy and Banking and Finance

EQF level 6

University of Malta, Imsida (Malta)

PERSONAL SKILLS

Mother tongue(s)

Maltese

Foreign language(s)

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING			
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production				
C2	C1	C1	C1	C1			
Ordinary level							
C1	C1	C2	C1	C1			
Intermedian / lovel							

English

Italian

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user Common European Framework of Reference for Languages - Self-assessment grid

Communication skills

- good communication skills gained through interaction with many clients and customers in different working environments

Organisational / managerial skills

- organisation and time management gained through assignments, examinations and work placements (through stock taking activities with various individuals and groups)

Digital skills

SELF-ASSESSMENT						
Information processing	Communication	Content creation	Safety	Problem- solving		
Proficient user	Proficient user	Independent user	Independent user	Proficient user		

Digital skills - Self-assessment grid

ECDL



- good command of office suite (word processing, presentation software, spread sheet)